Anna Galkina

Front-end developer







Email: anna.blackbird1@gmail.com



Phone: +7(962)9114695

Summary



Hi, my name's Anna and I'm a front-end developer (React/Redux stack). Also I'm very interested in React native. I'm result oriented, well-organized and responsible, team-player. Highly ambitious and extremely motivated. I'm so passioned about front-end development. Before IT entry, I had a huge working experience in internationals companies at marketing department including day-to-day communication with external and internal business partners. I developed and implemented brand strategy, analyzed customer researches.

Technical skills

Programming Languages: TypeScript, JavaScript (including modern approaches async/await, ES6)

JavaScript libraries and frameworks: React, React Native, Angular

Store management: Redux, Redux-toolkit, Redux-thunks, ReduxDev Tools

REST API: Axios, WebSocket, Postman, Swagger, basic back-end skills (express),

Styles and Design: CSS Preprocessors (SASS), CSS modules, Responsive web design, MUI, Antd, Figma

Routing: React-router-dom v5 and v6

Tests: Jest Unit Tests, Storybook, Snapshot, Test Driven Development (TDD)

Flow: Git, GitHub, GitHub pages Containers: Docker

Atlassian stack: Jira, Confluence

Experience

• Developed authentication features: registration, login, and password recovery

Freelance

Front-end Aug 2022- Nov2022

- Developed reusable components
- Wrote Unit Tests • Debug and fix programming bugs
- Tracked tasks in Jira
- Worked with git
- Brand annual strategy development. Developing and monitoring brand budget. Product pricing strategy • Evaluation annual brand and product sales potential, creating annual sales flow. Identification of product gaps and
- incremental opportunities for growth • Launch of new brand preparation and execution: localization of global idea. Identification of consumer insights,
- needs and marketing trends; development of brand position and communication • Full leadership of launch and leverage with 360 o activation with digital and field support
- Effective product line up management (500 SKU), product portfolio optimization
- Day-to-day communication with external and internal business partners

Business achievements:

- Developed Strategy for nail segment. The highest sales in 5 years horizon • Developed from scratch 1st Face Shade Selection event to overcome key purchase barrier. Grew +26% in Sales
- Actively contributed to new millenials brand launch, including:1st time in Avon launch Brochure digitalization,
- maximizing festival occasion through leading festival mark Event, including integration to the biggest millenials festival Picnic Afisha. Led Mark web site development, the only one fully branded page on my.avon.ru strongly inline with brand. Developed new different format of recruitment tools for sales department - layout: left

Avon

Avon

Junior brand manager Skin Care category

Brand manager Make-up category

February 2015 - March 2018

July 2013 – to February 2015

• Category Value segment management

- Launch of new product segment leading: consumer research communication, BTL and ATL activities
- Market analyzes Skin Care category budgeting

and Skin Care brands

Procter & Gamble Specialist in Marketing Strategy and

Planning

October 2010 - July 2013

• Preparation of reports and analysis of all relevant Marketing information • Participation in implementation of marketing strategies

• Organization BTL Events. Design, development and production of the POS materials and souvenirs for Hair Care

 Making a tender between agencies • Logistic organization and documentation support

Work and Travel (USA) June 2008 - August 2008

Participation in International Exchange Program - Work & Travel USA

Projects

Todo List Todo List Website

Todo List app with ability to login, create different todo lists with tasks and its descriptions, edit content and track status.

Technical stack: REST API, TS, React, Redux-toolkit, React-redux, React router dom v6, Axios, MUI, Formik, Jest.

https://AnyaGalkina.github.io/finance_tracker

Developed from scratch

Finance Tracker

Budget app that let you track expenditures and income. It's also give an opportunity to set goals and gradually save money to achieve the targets. I started this pet project as a way if learning React. I have learned many skills through this and been I'm very proud of having this in my portfolio. As I totally developed this one from scratch.

Technical stack: TS, React, Redux, React-redux, React router dom v6, Local Storage, React-Chartjs-2, MUI, React-Fontawesome, Jest, Uuid.

Learning Cards https://anyagalkina.github.io/cards/

Leading team work project

Learning cards app with ability to create your own profile account. Easy to create own packs with cards to learn in question/answer format and monitor your

study progress. Use search and filters to find packs created by other users. **Technical stack**: REST API, TS, React, Redux-toolkit, React-redux, React router dom v6, Axios, MUI, Formik, Jest.

Social Network

https://anyagalkina.github.io/samurai-way

App was developed with class container components and refactored with functional components and hooks

Social Network for front-end developers: Login and update profile info. Follow real users. Easy to chat thanks to WebSocket connection. Listen music at music library. Read TechCrunch news and share them with one click.

Technical stack: REST API, Axios, TS, React, Redux, React-redux, React router dom v5, Antd, Formik, Jest, Uuid

https://t.me/Pole_Training_Adviser_bot

Telegram Bot

Training adviser for pole sportsmen which help them to choose exercises for different levels.

Technical stack: Javascript, Telegraf, Node-telegram-bot-api

Languages

Russian: Native

English: Upper intermediate

Spanish: Basic

React/Angular front-end developer. React Native developer

Education

2022

It-Incubator

The App Brewery

Moscow State

2021

Web Development Course.

Linguistic University 2005 - 2011

Master of Science in Applied Economics Masters degree with honors

A Little More About Me

Some of my other interests and hobbies are: Sport, Diving, Snowboarding

Anna Galkina - anna.blackbird1@gmail.com